Next up, batting!
I'd like to go to batting!
Sir, have you ever batted before?
No!
No?
No, sir.
Have you ever had a bang?
Yes, I've held it with my fingers.
I've held it with my fingers vertically.
But not often.
Then let's try batting.
This is a variety show where Ana tries all kinds of things.
Wow! Yes! Fast! Fast?
I'm pretty fast.
Well, Anna, let's see what you can do.
It's just up ahead, right there.
Stand there and shoot it the way you want to shoot it!
Here we go!
What? Oh, my God! Ow! Ow!
Hurts?
That's good.
You've got the grip right from the start.
It's normal.
The first time you do it, you'll have a high hand.
But you instinctively know how to do it.
That's great.
This is going to be a good player.
You're gonna be a good player! You're gonna be a good player!
This is one!
I can see the ball.
I'm gonna be a good player!
Are you having fun?
It's fun!
Great! Nice batting! Yes! You've got great body vision, and your bat is touching the ground. Really?
Really? - Yes. You can be Leiwa's buttstress!
No?
Just touch it.
I'll tell you one more thing.
It's still powerful.
It's amazing.
Once you get a hit...
I want to hit it, I want to hit it, I want to hit it, I want to hit it
I'll go forward like this.
Why not go forward?
If you go forward, the ball will come from the other side.
If you go to meet it...
You'll miss each other.
So you just have to pick it up as it comes.
With the bat.
Like this?
That's right.
But there's really nothing to correct about my form.
What? Really?
You've got a lot of talent.
Stop.
Stop?
Stop what comes from the other side.
It's easier to stop if you have a sense of rhythm.
So let's say you have a bat.
Do you have a favorite food?
Soup
Soup.
Soup?
If it was soup...
soup
Stop here
sense of rhythm here.
If you go before "soup soup soup soup", it's a seal thing! Rhythm sense here seal thing
If you go to the front, it's a sticker!
On the contrary, it's rather difficult to hit it.
So when you think the timing is right
The stickers stop
When the sticker comes
When you see the sticker coming, hold the object in front of your navel and wave it in the air.
Shake it while saying once
Green
The one who knows.
I'm going. I know.
Where is it right? That's a good question.Where is it right? Well, that's a good question, because the core of the bat is...
This mark.
The mark on the bat.
The harder you hit it.
the farther it flies.
So the surface here
the surface of the core, the surface of the mark.
Tightly bind it.
Yes, sir.
With what you know
What you know
Yes
What we know
So wonderful
In what we know
Something to know
Eh, okay
Yes, yes
To.
That's great.
It's great that you want to be good at it, and you're really conveying that.
I'm going to try it.
I'd like to see it.
He's holding it like this, isn't he?
I'm with Matsuda-san of the Giants.
Only Matsuda-san can do it.
He is the only one who holds like this.
Basically, the hands are aligned, so that centrifugal force and the head can work more effectively.
Here...
Seal
The thing.
I didn't hit anything.
That was fast.
Nice ball.
Seal thing
I'm scared
I'm afraid it's going to crack!
Sticker thing that broke down the hitter! Scary! I'm afraid it's going to break!
Batter
It would be great if this pitcher crushed it.
Nice sound!
Like now.
Stickers.
I'm gonna hit it right here.
I can't help it if I go in front of it.
Stickers.
I just happened to win this one.
If you go to the front, you have less chance of hitting it.
I'll hit it here.
Seal in bono
Oh, great.
Like this.
Don't go inside.
In front of you.
Seal in bono.
Like this.
Seal in bonos! Seal thing!
If you guess here
How many centimeters are left to guess?
It's already a margin of error.
That's where the timing is.
May I?
Oh, great!
Index finger.
You're not using it.
I'm talking.
Index finger, sure.
Hey, you're lifting your index finger.
Why are you lifting your index finger?
Well, you know, to relax.
Relax?
If you grip with all of your fingers, you'll tense up your shoulders.
It's hard to hear the core of the head.
I'm the type of person who tends to put a lot of pressure on my shoulders, so I do it this way.
Okay, Ano channel.
Please try to get the rhythm while saying out loud what you know.
What do you know?Who knows?
You're right.
Yes, now.
You know what?
Yes, the ball is coming to me.
You don't have to go for it, the ball will come to you
Trust the ball.
Oh, great.
That's great.
Trust the ball.
Trust yourself and the ball!
Oh!
Know it!
Keep your voice up! Whatever you like that makes it easier to get the rhythm!
Know what!
Ooh!
Do you have any other favorite foods?
Yes, I do.
What do you like?
Rice!
Oh! That's good! Rice with takikomi!
That's good! Let's do takikomi-gohan!
Mash it up nicely with rice!
Yes!
Rice! Rice!
Rice!
Let's mash it up good and hard with rice! Mash the rice balls with the rice!
Crush the ball firmly with takikomi-gohan!
Cooked rice!
Oh!
You got it!
Rice in a bowl!
Ooh!
Rice with sake-komi!
Oh!
That's two bases!
Shiba the ball up tight!
Takikomi gohan!
Oh!
Can you go up?
That's great!
Mimigarh?
Mimigar is fine!
Mimigar!
Let's do this! Mimigurumi, ears, ears, let's go with that.
Ears...
Oh, wait, I'm just looking.
That was just an error.
It's okay.
I'm adjusting.
My ear.
Oh, nice swing.
It's hard for my ears.
Do you want to change your ears?
Let's see...
Fluce
Fluce, fluoche, fluoche! Fluce! Fluce!
Fluce!
Shell, you're lying!
Just a little bit!
Fluce!
Fluce! Le! Fluce! Che!
Hu! Fuh! Le! Che!
F! FU! Che!
Fluce!
Flürcher! Flürcher! Yeah! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Fluture!
Fulcher!
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, my God!
Is it done?
It's done.
No, it's great.
What, you could have done more?What, you could do more?
You want to hit more?
I'm trying to grow up.
My heart wants to grow.
Let's keep on hitting!
What do you like?
It doesn't have to be food.
I'm easy to put my energy into.
I also like ramen
Ray Men
Raymen
Raymen also like Raymen! Ray Men! Ray Men!
Raymen!
Ray men!
That's it!
Let's do one swing! Hard!
Ray men!
Whoo! Ray Men!
So powerful!
Ray men! Isn't it! Raymen daho!
Now that's a response! One more pitch!
Reimen!
That's it! Nice one!
Let's hit it then!
If you're going to lift your leg with a "le", then "le"!
Rey!
Re! Re!
Re!
Raise! Le!
Le!
Le! Le! Lei! Men! Men! Le! Le! Raise! Le! Le! Up! Le! It! Y!
Men!
Le!
men!
Men! Men!
Why? It's done.
Re!
Men!
That's it!
Let's go with that.
How about boiled fish?
Grilled fish? Grilled fish!
Grilled fish! Grilled! Grilled! Grilled fish? Grilled fish? Grilled fish!
Grilled.
grilled
Fish.
Isn't this place cool? Pitcher.
Raise the pitcher.
Grill
Grill.
Fish!
Fish, yes.
Grill.
Grilled.
Fish!
Fish.
Oh!
That's good.
One more pitch.
Yaki
Fish, good seg! Now!
Oh! Nice seg!
Now that's a good one.
Oh!
You're pulling!
That's a first! He went that way!
Proof that I'm not late.
That's it!
That's great.
Nice grilled fish.
That's the one.
Grilled fish.
You can put it in the palm of your handYou can put it in the nadir.
grilled fish
Oh!
These two are so cute.
Even the awesome reimen is good oh! Wow, this bill.
Amazing. I don't care if it's a reimen.
Rei!
Reimen!
Nngh!
But okay.
Ray men!
Oh!
Wow!
You swallow fast!
Nice Reimen!
Shrimp sushi?
Shrimp sushi!
Sushi! Shrimp sushi! Shrimp sushi! Shrimp sushi! Shrimp sushi!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Shrimp sushi!
Oh! Quick!
Or maybe it's shrimp sushi!
Shrimp sushi!
Shrimp... Shrimp sushi... shrimp sushi... shrimp sushi... shrimp sushi...
How did I win?
Shrimp!
How did you win?
What just happened?
Shrimp sushi.
It's gone!
Shrimp...
Let go of yourself!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Not a big deal, not a big deal, not a big deal, not a big deal, not a big deal, not a big deal, not a big deal, not a big deal No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Big!
Shrimp big!
Yes!
I see. I see.
Large prawns.
Sushi.
Very dexterous.
You're very good at what you do.
Nice batting!
Which one was the easiest to hit?
But the last half of the sushi with shrimps is nice.
Oh, that's great!
Shrimp sushi!
Oh!
Oh, but then again, that's where the shrimp oohs come in.
Not oh, shrimp ooh!
Not "Ooh!" but "Ooh!
Shrimp ooh! Oh! Please do it from now on, and I'll be back to see how much you've grown.
Don't miss a thing.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
Nice match.
Ana Channel, subscribe to our channel!
ED.